<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="nav_header_academy">Academy</string>

    <string name="nav_base">Base information</string>
    <string name="nav_organization">Organization</string>
    <string name="nav_local_academy">Local academy ES</string>
    <string name="nav_apply">Who can apply</string>
    <string name="nav_how_apply">How to apply</string>

    <string name="nav_base_info_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
        <head></head>
        <body style="text-align:justify;background-color : transparent;">
        Network Academy Program is electronic study model which includes web-based basic materials,
        on-line testing, students’ current knowledge tracking, training and support for instructors and as
        well practical laboratory work.
        Networking Academy Program is carried out in universities, secondary schools,
        high schools and other educational institutions.
        Network Academy Program was formally established 1997 by most eminent companies concerning network technologies Cisco Systems.
        It represents a course which lasts eight semesters / 560 classes
        Via course, students are prepared for acquirement of industrial sertificates like
         Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) and Cisco Certified Network Professional (CCNP).
        The program combines lectures and on-line studying with practical laboratory exercises where
        students can show their acquired knowledge by working on real networks. After four semesters
        and 280 classes students are completely trained for exam 640-801 for gaining CCNA sertificate.
        CCNA sertificate is the first step in Cisco Career Certification program, which ends with CCIE sertificate,
         most respected sertificate in the field of computer comunication. Materials for course preperation (curriculum and other materials)
         as well as tests which participants take are available on Internet by using CNAMS (Cisco Networking Academy Management System).
        Special attention was dedicated to use and check of acquired theory knowledge which is being done in especially equipped laboratories.
        </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="academy_organization_part1">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
        <head></head>
        <body style="text-align:justify;background-color : transparent;">
        The educational institusion which implements Networking Academy Program is Cisco Networking Academy.
        Cisco Academy system is hierarchically organised, like is show on next pictures:
        </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="academy_organization_part2">
        There are three levels of academies:
    </string>

    <string name="academy_organization_sub1">
        Local Academy is an institution which maintains one or more Network Academy courses for students.
        Local academy is responsable for providing enviroment for maintaining courses.
    </string>

    <string name="academy_organization_sub2">
        Regional Academy is an institution which provides support to Local Academies in one geographical area.
        Regional Academy provides training of local instructors for every course semester. Roll of Regional Academy, as well,
        is to give continuous support to Local Academies about establishing classes, technical questions, questions about material and programmes etc.
    </string>

    <string name="academy_organization_sub3">
        CATC (Cisco Academy Training Center) is an institution which gives support to Regional Academies in the aforementioned ways.
    </string>

    <string name="academy_organization_part3">
        All administrative jobs concerning Network Academy Program are being done using one simple Web application.
    </string>

</resources>