<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="nav_header_cisco">Cisco</string>

    <string name="nav_goals">Goals</string>
    <string name="nav_inventions">Inventions</string>
    <string name="nav_connection">Connection</string>
    <string name="nav_mission">Mission and vision</string>

    <string name="nav_golas_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
        <head></head>
        <body style="text-align:justify;">
        Cisco was founded 1984 and it is among the founders of modern internet.
        Engeneers of Cisco had a major role in stimulating developement of IP protocol (Internet Protocol),
        language which is stil the foundation of Internet.
        Today, Cisco solutions, are in many networks in companies, faculties, administrations and governments world wide.
        The infrastructure of Cisco transmits 80% of data through Internet.
        The company employs 36.500 employees.
        Cisco headquarters are in San Hose, California, USA.
        Larger business units are in Research Triangle Park in North Carolina, Chemsford,
        Massachusetts; Stockley Park, Great Britain and Sidney, Australia.
        In sixty states all around the world Cisco has got over 430 offices for sale and customer support.
        </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="nav_inventions_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
        <head></head>
        <body style="text-align:justify;">
        Cisco makes products and invents technologies so to make use of the Internet much more simple and dynamic.
        From Internet research and development laboratories came 70% new Cisco technologies.
        Optical networks, IP routing, transmission of voice and video data via
        IP protocol, wireless technology, control of contents, networks for placement of data,
        are all technologies of future which came from Cisco research centers.
        </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="nav_connection_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
        <head></head>
        <body style="text-align:justify;">
        Aware of thorough changes which Internet brings in every-day-life and in our way of work, Cisco based his own organisation on Internet and local networks.
        Cisco was among those who first used networks to support a client, sell a product, educate employees and financial management.
        Solutions which Cisco suggests to his clients are proven and a result of their own practise.
        It is without a doubt that just that kind of starting point in e-culture made Cisco company a real world wide supplier of network solutions for Internet.
        Those solutions are fit for all important aspects of good operation of network:
        switching, routing, security, wireless technologies, voice transmission via IP protocol,
        data placement, administration, transfer of data and Long Reach Ethernet.
        The most modern technologies are necessary to every company wishing to develope to keep pace with the time.
        </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="nav_mission_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
        <head></head>
        <body style="text-align:justify;">
        To mould the future of the Internet by creating values and incredible
        benefits for our clients, partners, workers and investors.
        Internet is changing the way we live, work, play and study.
        </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>